kilaru Go Charan

Andhra Pradesh, India



gocharan98@gmail.com



7338496989



linkedin.com/in/kilaru-go-charan-9219501a1

Summary

Experienced Member with a demonstrated history of working in the computer and network security industry. Skilled in Hindi, CTF, Presentations, Public Speaking, and English. Strong operations professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science from Lovely Professional University.

Experience



CTF team manager

NOOB 4rMY

Apr 2020 - Present (10 months +)



Member

CyberHack

Mar 2020 - Present (11 months +)



Campus Ambassador

Indian Road Safety Campaign

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019 (3 months)

created awareness regarding the Indian road safety.

Campus Ambassador

Cybervie-Ionots Technologies Pvt Ltd

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019 (3 months)

conducted awareness programs regarding the courses offered by the company and helped them to increasing their marketing.



Campus Ambassador

Wissenaire, IIT Bhubaneswar

Sep 2019 - Dec 2019 (4 months)

creating awareness regarding the courses offered and events called by them.

Education



Lovely Professional University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science 2019 - 2023

Vignan's Foundation for Science, Technology & Research

matriculate and senior secondary education, class 6th to 12th 2014 - 2019

Licenses & Certifications

Certified Ethical Hacker (CEH) - EC-Council

Skills

```
CTF player • Public Speaking • Seminar Presentations • Presentations • English • Hindi • Cybersecurity • CTF • Blogger • Ethical Hacking
```